A Guide to the University of Virginia Health System Marketing Communications collection, 1857-2006, bulk 1950-2000
Historical Collections, Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
Historical Collections, Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
University of Virginia Health System Marketing Communications Collection, 1857-2006, bulk 1950-2000
Historical Collections, Claude Moore Health Sciences Library, University of Virginia
MS-68
10 boxes measuring 10.5 inches x 12.5 inches x 15.5 inches; total of 10.5 linear feet
University of Virginia
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Some access restrictions may apply to photographic materials.
Acquisition Information
The materials were transferred to the Claude Moore Health Sciences Library for preservation from the University of Virginia Health System’s Marketing Communications Department.
Scope and Content
The University of Virginia Health System Marketing Communications collection consists of 5 series. Series I through Series IV contain 737 processed folders in 6 records boxes. The images in this collection were created by and/or for the University of Virginia Health System’s Department of Marketing Communications to document the people, premises, and events of the UVA Health System, the UVA School of Medicine, and the UVA School of Nursing. These four series hold photographic prints, negatives, and slides, and also contain some published materials and assorted Marketing Communications papers and correspondence related to past Marketing Communications publications. The images provide a visual history of the University of Virginia’s work in medical education and medical care throughout the twentieth century. Series V of the collection contains 4 boxes of unprocessed slides, image CDs, and zip disks. At the time of processing some non-Health System materials present with the original acquisition were transferred to the Albert and Shirley Small Special Collections Library and the Arthur J. Morris Law Library.
Arrangement
The records are arranged in four series with the documents within each series arranged according to subject matter and chronology. The series are:
Series I, Departmental materials, 1907-2002
Series II, Buildings and grounds, 1857-2006
Series III, Events and people, 1873-2006
Series IV, Marketing publications and related materials, 1991-2004
Series V, Unprocessed materials
Contents List
- Series I: Departmental materials, 1907-2002
  This series consists of images from various departments within the UVA Health System.
  The records are arranged into sub-series according to department. Items in each subseries are arranged chronologically.
  - Health System Administration, 1970-2001
    - Medical Records Office: Mrs. Taylor, Mrs. Davis, Miss Tagland, Miss Thompson, 1970 May (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Hospital Advisory Board: John Ashley, Leigh Middleditch, 1985 October (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Awards Banquet for Personnel Administration, with Pat Martin, 1988 (Box-folder 1:3)
    - Alex Sawyer, Hospital Administration, 1989 May (Box-folder 1:4)
    - Michael Halseth, Hospital Administration, 1990 January 5 (Box-folder 1:5)
    - Robert Reynolds, Vice President for Health Sciences, 1990 April 4 (Box-folder 1:6)
      Photographed by J. Biondo
    - Jules Levine, Associate Vice President for Health Sciences, 1990 May (Box-folder 1:7)
    - Linda L. Thompson, Medical Center Fiscal Assistant, 2001 (Box-folder 1:8)
    - Edward Howell with Wren D. Olivier and other unidentified staff, circa 2006 (Box-folder 1:9)
    - Admitting, Business, Auditing, and Data Processing offices, undated (Box-folder 1:10)
    - Beth A. Bailey, Post-baccalaureate Pre-medical Program Director, undated (Box-folder 1:11)
    - Edward Howell with Irving Kron and other Medical Center staff members, undated (Box-folder 1:12)
    - Harvey E. Jordan, Dean of the School of Medicine (1940-1949), undated (Box-folder 1:13)
    - Vernon W. Lippard, Dean of the School of Medicine (1949-1953), undated (Box-folder 1:14)
    - Tonchi Vest, Admissions, undated (Box-folder 1:15)
  - Anatomy, 1907-1989
    - Anatomy Group with cadavers and skeleton, 1907 (Box-folder 1:16)
      Not in order: Dr. Whitehead (Richard Henry), Dr. Norford (J.E.), Class of 1910: (William Henry) Baughman, (John Henry) Neff, (George Hermann) Lang, (Lewis) Booker, Cocke, (Mark Roy) Faville, (Joseph Benjamin) Waples, (Charles Brown) Crawford, Brevard.
    - Anatomy Group with cadavers and skeleton, circa 1907-1910 (Box-folder 1:17)
      Faculty and Class of 1910: W.C. Gibson, Suffolk VA; R.H. Whitehead, Professor of Anatomy; J.A. Norford, Instructor in Anatomy; Ellis N. Ivey (?), Suffolk VA; H.W. Jackson, Jr., Keswick VA; W.D. Haden, Charlottesville VA; B.S. Snowden, North Carolina; Henderson Irwin, Charlotte NC; L.H. Lewis, Harrisonburg VA.
      Separated Materials Note
      Item stored with oversize materials in the Historical Collections Photographs Room.
    - Students in the Anatomy Laboratory, 1941 (Box-folder 1:18)
    - Charles Flickenger, Anatomy, 1989 November 29 (Box-folder 1:19)
      Photographed by J. Biondo; taken in Jordan Hall.
    - J. David Deck, Anatomy, undated (Box-folder 1:20)
    - Harvey Jordan, Anatomy, undated (Box-folder 1:21)
    - James Kindred, Anatomy, undated (Box-folder 1:22)
    - James E. Kindred, Anatomy, and Cyst diagrams with unidentified x-rayundated (Box-folder 1:23)
      Diagrams and x-ray in envelope marked “Dr. Kindred”
    - Edwin Pullen, Anatomy, undated (Box-folder 1:24)
  - Anesthesiology, 1987-1993
    - Bill Arnold, Anesthesiology, 1987 October 16 (Box-folder 1:25)
    - Robert Epstein, Anesthesiology, 1989 December 12 - 1990 April 19 (Box-folder 1:26)
    - Anesthesiology Group, with Robert Epstein, Chair, circa 1990-1992 (Box-folder 1:27)
    - Frederic (Fritz) Berry, Anesthesiology, 1991 (Box-folder 1:28)
    - Marie-Louise Birmingham, Anesthesiology, circa 1993 (Box-folder 1:29)
    - Cosmo A. DiFazio, Anesthesiology, undated (Box-folder 1:30)
    - Robert Epstein, Anesthesiology Chair, undated (Box-folder 1:31)
    - Karen Schwenzer, Anesthesiology, undated (Box-folder 1:32)
  - Basic Sciences, 1989-1990
    This group comprises of several departments, including Biochemistry, Biomedical Engineering, Microbiology, Neuroscience, and Pharmacology.
    - Alfred Chanutin, Biochemistry, 1964 February (Box-folder 1:33)
    - Alfred Chanutin, Biochemistry, 1966 June (Box-folder 1:34)
    - Alfred Chanutin, Biochemistry, 1968 March 18 (Box-folder 1:35)
    - Alfred Chanutin, Biochemistry, 1970 October 19 (Box-folder 1:36)
    - Alfred Chanutin, Biochemistry, 1973 May 15 (Box-folder 1:37)
    - Robert Meredith MacLeod, Biochemistry/Internal Medicine, undated (Box-folder 1:38)
    - Ernst O. Attinger, Biomedical Engineering, at Stacey Hall, 1990 January 17 (Box-folder 1:39)
    - Thomas Hutchinson, Biomedical Engineering, at Stacey Hall, 1990 January 17 (Box-folder 1:40)
    - John Herr, Biomedical Engineering, undated (Box-folder 1:41)
    - Microbiology Group with (left to right:) Catherine Russell, Alto E. Feller, Wesley Volk, and L. Lee Kupferbergcirca 1952 (Box-folder 1:42)
    - Gerald Goldstein, Microbiology/Internal Medicine, 1964 May 20 (Box-folder 1:43)
    - Alto E. Feller, Microbiology, undated (Box-folder 1:44)
    - Gerald Goldstein, Microbiology/Internal Medicine, undated (Box-folder 1:45)
    - Wesley A. Volk, Microbiology, undated (Box-folder 1:46)
    - Mike Webber Laboratory, Microbiology, undated (Box-folder 1:47)
    - Oswald Steward, Neuroscience, 1990 July 24 (Box-folder 1:48)
      Photographed by J. Biondo in Cobb Hall
    - Joseph Larner, Pharmacology, 1989 December 6 (Box-folder 1:49)
    - Chalmers L. Gemmill, Pharmacologyundated (Box-folder 1:50)
    - Chalmers L. Gemmill (Pharmacology) and D.T. Watts, undated (Box-folder 1:51)
      C.L. Gemmill on right
    - Charles Slaughter Diploma from the University of Virginia School of Medicine, Physiology, 1876 (Box-folder 1:52)
    - W. Parker Anslow, Physiology, Chair, 1952 September 14 (Box-folder 1:53)
    - Robert M. Berne, Physiology, circa 1971 (Box-folder 1:54)
    - Physiology staff, with Takeyasu and Owens, 1990 March (Box-folder 1:55)
  - Behavioral Medicine and Psychiatry, 1972-1990
    - Norma J. Knorr, Psychiatry, 1970 November (Box-folder 1:56)
    - David C. Wilson, Behavioral Medicine and Psychiatry, circa 1972-1977 (Box-folder 1:57)
    - Norma J. Knorr, Psychiatry, Dean of the School of Medicine, 1979 (Box-folder 1:58)
    - Portrait of David C. Wilson and photographs of Blue Ridge Hospital, circa 1984 (Box-folder 1:59)
    - Psychiatry Group, 1988 April 5 (Box-folder 1:60)
    - Institute of Law and Psychiatry Group, 1988 (Box-folder 1:61)
    - Psychiatry Group at Blue Ridge Hospital, 1989 Spring (Box-folder 1:62)
    - Ian Stevenson, Behavioral Medicine and Psychiatry, 1989 December 5 (Box-folder 1:63)
    - John Buckman, Behavioral Medicine and Psychiatry at Blue Ridge Hospital, 1989 December 14 (Box-folder 1:64)
    - Department of Mental Health, Richmond, Awards at the Sheraton group photograph, with Elsie Little(?)1990 July 20 (Box-folder 1:65)
    - Behavioral Medicine and Psychiatry Group at Blue Ridge Hospital, with Wilford W. Spradlin, 1991 (Box-folder 1:66)
    - Behavioral Medicine and Psychiatry Group at Blue Ridge Hospital, with Wilford W. Spradlin, 1992 May (Box-folder 1:67)
    - J. Kim Penberthy, Psychiatry, 2004 Fall (Box-folder 1:68)
      Photographed by Jackson Smith for the Fall 2004 issue of Health Talk
    - Psychiatry Group, with Randolph Cantebury, undated (Box-folder 1:69)
    - David R. Hawkins, Psychiatry, undated (Box-folder 1:70)
    - Norman J. Knorr, Psychiatry, undated (Box-folder 1:71)
    - Jim Tucker, Child and Family Psychiatry, undated (Box-folder 1:72)
  - Biomedical Ethics, 1987-1989
    - MCI, Biomedical Committee, with N. Duke, 1987 February 13-14 (Box-folder 1:73)
      Photographed by H. Buz Goforth
    - Biomedical Committee outside Pavilion I, with Murray Howard, 1988 November 3 (Box-folder 1:74)
    - Center for Biomedical Ethics, 1989 June 9 (Box-folder 1:75)
      Submitted by ? Foubert
    - Center for Biomedical Ethics, 1989 June 6-12 (Box-folder 1:76)
  - Blue Ridge Hospital, 1987-1989
    - Charles B. Pearson (left) and Frank B. Stafford at Blue Ridge Hospital's newly opened West Wing, circa 1950 (Box-folder 1:77)
    - Blue Ridge Hospital meeting, with Linda Shank, circa 1987 April (Box-folder 1:78)
    - Blue Ridge Hospital Group, 1988 Spring (Box-folder 1:79)
    - Felicia Gaskins, Blue Ridge Hospital, 1989 December 14 (Box-folder 1:80)
    - Blue Ridge Sanatorium West Wing, with Charles B. Pearson and Frank B. Stafford, undated (Box-folder 1:81)
      C. Pearson on left in long, white coat.
  - Dentistry, 1991
    - Thomas Leinbach, Dentistry, 1991 February 15 (Box-folder 1:82)
  - Dermatology, 1965-1990
    - Dudley Crofford Smith, Dermatology, Founding Chairman, 1965 April 15 (Box-folder 1:83)
    - Peyton Weary, Dermatology, 1969 November 13 (Box-folder 1:84)
    - Peyton Weary, Dermatology, 1971 November 23 (Box-folder 1:85)
    - Peyton Weary, Dermatology, Chair (1976-1993), 1990 January 16 (Box-folder 1:86)
      Photographed by John Biondo for Jarcom Inc., for an issue of Dermatology: Point/Counterpoint
    - Dermatology Group, with Peyton Weary, Chair, Kenneth Greer, Barbara Wilson 1990 November (Box-folder 1:87)
    - Edward P. Cawley, Dermatology, undated (Box-folder 1:88)
  - Dietary and Nutrition Services, 1969-2002
    - Dietary Services, 1969 Fall (Box-folder 1:89)
    - Nellie Gray, Dietary, Employee of the Month, 1991 June (Box-folder 1:90)
    - Carol Rees Parrish, Nutrition Services, 2002 (Box-folder 1:91)
    - Food, Dietary Services undated (Box-folder 1:92)
  - Digestive Health Center Women's Clinic, 2000
    - Digestive Health Center Women’s Clinic article and photographs, with Cynthia Yoshida 2000 September 5 (Box-folder 1:93)
      Printed in The Link, 2000.
  - Emergency Medicine, 1987-2004
    - CPR Class, with Robert Reynolds, Emergency Medicine, 1987 May (Box-folder 1:94)
    - Pegasus Helicopter, crew, and patient on the Helipad, Emergency Medicine,circa 1987 (Box-folder 1:95A)
    - Pegasus Helicopter Artwork, 1989 September 1 (Box-folder 1:95B)
    - Emergency Medicine Residents, Class of 2004, circa 2004 (Box-folder 1:96)
      Includes Erin Mancuso, Heather Hollowell, Jennifer King, Monica Williams-Murphy, Claire M. Urbina, Katherine Haltiwanger, Jesse Pines, David Johnson, and staff member Terry Moore.
    - Bryan Frost, Emergency Medicine, undated (Box-folder 1:97)
    - J. Stephen Huff, Emergency Medicine, undated (Box-folder 1:98)
    - William Gaines Talbott, First Med at Pantops, Emergency Medicine Departmentundated (Box-folder 1:99)
    - Staff photographs, Emergency Medicine, undated (Box-folder 1:100)
      Includes Edward Fenton, Earl Maready, Stephen Small, Mike Somers, Jeffrey Norvell, Jeffrey Ferguson, Tray Dobson, Steven Mitchell, Terry Moore, Steven Moye
  - Family Medicine, 1977-2001
    - Photographs for Family Medicine Residency Program brochure, with Lewis Barnett, David Waters, Sam Miller, Gladys Bowman (Cole?), circa 1977 (Box-folder 1:101)
    - Richard Lindsay and two others, Department of Medicine and Family Practice, 1988 (Box-folder 1:102)
    - Family Practice Group at Blue Ridge Hospital, with L. Barnett, 1989 May 19 (Box-folder 1:103)
    - Lewis Barnett, Family Practice, Chair, 1989 November 1 (Box-folder 1:104)
      Photographed by C. Hodge
    - Mason Lee, Patient and Community Health Education, 1990 October 22 (Box-folder 1:105)
    - Family Practice Medical Students, 1991 June 10 (Box-folder 1:106)
    - Family Hemophilia Day, with Ann Smutz, 1991 June 15 (Box-folder 1:107)
    - Richard B. Hays, Family Medicine, 1992 July (Box-folder 1:108)
    - Primary Care/Family Medicine Publicity photographs, circa 1995 (Box-folder 1:109)
      Photographed by Bill Faust
    - Staff photographs, Stoney Creek Office and Crossroads Program, 2000-2001 June 28 (Box-folder 1:110)
      Pictured: Steven Heim, Charles Cole, Andrea Tribastone, Dan McCarter, Robin Smoot, Evalyn Brown, Susie Ladd, Debra Cote, Leah Gaulton, Laurel Wright, Michelle Spencer, Anne Mounsey, Charlotte Woods, some unidentified.
    - Andrea Tribastone, Family Medicine, 2001 August 29 (Box-folder 1:111)
    - Sim S. Galazka, Family Medicine, 2001 August (Box-folder 1:112)
    - Steven W. Heim, Family Medicine/Primary Care, 2001 (Box-folder 1:113)
    - Craig K. Seto, Family Medicine, undated (Box-folder 1:114)
  - Health Sciences Library, 1987-1997
    - LIS Unveiling at the Health Sciences Library, with Terry Thorkildson, Don Detmer, Rich Peterson, and Gretchen N. Arnold, circa 1987 (Box-folder 1:115)
    - Health Sciences Library, with Ken Crispell and Lawrence Altman, 1988 February - 1988 September (Box-folder 1:116)
    - Medical Artifacts and Rare Books, Health Sciences Library, 1988 February - 1988 September (Box-folder 1:117)
    - Health Sciences Library events, patrons, and facilities, 1989 (Box-folder 1:118)
    - Medical Artifacts, Health Sciences Library, 1990 February 23 (Box-folder 1:119)
    - Linda Watson, Health Sciences Library Director, 1990 May (Box-folder 1:120)
    - Health Sciences Library card catalog, patrons, and displays, 1990 (Box-folder 1:121)
    - Heart Association Gathering, Health Sciences Library, with Joan E. Klein, Linda Watson, 1991 February 4 (Box-folder 1:122)
    - School of Medicine Class of 1947 50th Reunion Luncheon, hosted by the Health Sciences Library, with Linda Watson, M.C., Wilhelm, and Jean Wilhelm, 1997 May (Box-folder 1:123)
    - Health Sciences Library Group, with Gretchen Naisawald, undated (Box-folder 1:124)
    - Health Sciences Library negatives, with Gretchen Naisawald, undated (Box-folder 1:125)
    - Historical Collections lecture at the Health Sciences Library, with Joan Ecktencamp Klein, Linda Watson, Gretchen Naisawald, undated (Box-folder 1:126)
    - Joan E. Klein with Dr. Thomas Hunter at the Health Sciences Library, undated (Box-folder 1:127)
    - Wilhelm Moll, Health Sciences Library Director, undated (Box-folder 1:128)
    - Patient and Family Health Collection Open House, undated (Box-folder 1:129)
  - Medical Center Housekeeping, circa 1952
    - Stewart Fuller, Hospital Housekeeping, circa 1952 (Box-folder 1:130)
  - Medical Technology, 1986-1992
    - Medical Technology Group, with Robin Herring, 1986 (Box-folder 1:131)
    - Medical Technology Group, 1988 (Box-folder 1:132)
    - Medical Technology Group, circa 1989 (Box-folder 1:133)
    - Medical Technology Group, with Mary Ellen Kolakis, 1990 February 14 (Box-folder 1:134)
    - Medical Technology Group, 1990 (Box-folder 1:135)
    - Clinical Lab Group, Medical Technology, 1991 June (Box-folder 1:136)
    - Medical Technology Group, 1992 (Box-folder 1:137)
  - Medicine, circa 1956-2004
    This subseries contains items relevant to the sub-disciplines within the Department of Medicine, including Asthma, Allergy & Immunology, Cardiology, Endocrinology, Gastroenterology, General Medicine, Hematology Oncology, Infectious Diseases, Nephrology, Pulmonary Medicine, and Rheumatology, as well as general Internal Medicine staff and groups.
    - Oscar Swineford, Jr., Asthma, Allergy, and Immunology, undated (Box-folder 1:138)
    - Oscar Swineford, Jr., Asthma, Allergy, and Immunology, undated (Box-folder 1:139)
    - Julian Beckwith, Internal Medicine - Cardiology, 1960 December (Box-folder 1:140)
    - Cardiology Group, with George Beller, 1988 (Box-folder 1:141)
    - Cardiology Group, with George Beller, 1989 May 16 (Box-folder 1:142)
    - Cardiology Group, with George Beller, 1990 June 12 (Box-folder 1:143)
    - Cardiology Group, with George Beller, 1991 (Box-folder 1:144)
    - John P. DiMarco, Cardiology, 1991 (Box-folder 1:145)
    - Cardiology Group, with George Beller, 1992 (Box-folder 1:146)
    - UVA Heart Center team members: Dearing W. Johns, Anne Hedelt, Robert S. Gibson, Melynda Zarzyski, and Teller Swett, circa 2004 (Box-folder 1:147)
      Photograph from Health Talk Fall 2004
    - Carlos Ayers, Cardiology, undated (Box-folder 1:148)
    - Julian Beckwith, Cardiology, undated (Box-folder 1:149)
    - Julian R. Beckwith, Internal Medicine - Cardiology, undated (Box-folder 1:150)
    - George Beller, Cardiology, undated (Box-folder 1:151)
    - Camp Training Center, undated (Box-folder 1:152)
    - Cardiology Group, with George Beller, undated (Box-folder 1:153)
    - Cardiology Group, with George Beller, undated (Box-folder 1:154)
    - Cardiology Group, with George Beller, undated (Box-folder 1:155)
    - Cardiology Group, with George Beller, undated (Box-folder 1:156)
    - UVA Heart Center, undated (Box-folder 1:157)
    - A.G. Kfoury, Cardiology, undated (Box-folder 1:158)
    - J. Edwin Wood Sr., Cardiology, undated (Box-folder 1:159)
    - Kenneth Crispell, Endocrinology, 1963 January 13 (Box-folder 2:1)
    - Endocrinology Group, with Robert Carey, 1986 (Box-folder 2:2)
      First Row, left to right: ?, Ken Crispell, Robert Carey, John Owen, Michael Thorner; Second row, left to right: ?,?, John Dunn, Jim Craig, ?
    - Robert Carey, Endocrinology, Chair1988 (Box-folder 2:3)
    - Robert Carey, Endocrinology, School of Medicine Dean, 1995 March (Box-folder 2:4)
    - Kenneth Crispell, Endocrinology, undated (Box-folder 2:5)
    - Johannes Veldhuis, Endocrinology, undated (Box-folder 2:6)
    - Gastroenterology Group, with Richard McCallum, 1984 May 5 (Box-folder 2:7)
    - Gastroenterology Group, with Richard McCallum, 1987 (Box-folder 2:8)
    - David D. Stone, Gastroenterology, 1989 November 16 (Box-folder 2:9)
    - Richard McCallum, Gastroenterology, 1989 December 7 (Box-folder 2:10)
    - Gastroenterology Group with Richard McCallum, 1990 June 15 (Box-folder 2:11)
    - Suffie Hoffman, Gastroenterology lab?, 1990 December 3 (Box-folder 2:12)
    - Gastroenterology Group with McCallum, 1991 June 21 (Box-folder 2:13)
      McCallum in first row; Barry Marshall, James Roche in second row.
    - Gastroenterology Group, with Richard McCallum, 1992 (Box-folder 2:14)
    - Peter B. Ernst, Gastroenterology, 2002 (Box-folder 2:15)
    - Jenny M. Buzan, Gastroenterology Lab, undated (Box-folder 2:16)
    - Martha Dudley, Gastroenterology, undated (Box-folder 2:17)
    - Wael M. El-Rifai, Gastroenterology, undated (Box-folder 2:18)
    - Karen B. Fink, Physician’s Assistant, Gastroenterology and Hepatology, with Danielle M. Harris, undated (Box-folder 2:19)
    - Gastroenterology Group, with Richard McCallum and James Roche, undated (Box-folder 2:20)
    - Jim Respass, Gastroenterology, undated (Box-folder 2:21)
    - Alfred J. Bollet, Preventative Medicine (General Medicine), 1965 March 2 (Box-folder 2:22)
    - Leslie J. Blackhall, General Medicine/Geriatrics and Palliative Care, undated (Box-folder 2:23)
    - John Staige Davis IV, Preventative Medicine (General Medicine), undated (Box-folder 2:24)
    - William S. Jordan, Preventative Medicine (General Medicine), undated (Box-folder 2:25)
    - Jennifer Marks, General Medicine, undated (Box-folder 2:26)
    - Hematology Oncology Group, with Peter Quesenberry, 1988 June 27 (Box-folder 2:27)
    - Munsey Wheby, Hematology Oncology, 1989 December 7 (Box-folder 2:28)
    - Imad Tabbara, Hematology Oncology, undated (Box-folder 2:29)
    - Oscar Thorpe, Hematology Oncology, undated (Box-folder 2:30)
    - Gerald Mandell, Infectious Diseases, 1989 November 22 (Box-folder 2:31)
    - Barry Farr, Infectious Diseases, 1989 November 29 (Box-folder 2:32)
    - Jack Gwaltney, Infectious Diseases, 1989 December 12 (Box-folder 2:33)
    - Frederick Hayden, Infectious Diseases, 1990 November 21 (Box-folder 2:34)
    - Barry Farr, Infectious Diseases, 2002 August 13 (Box-folder 2:35)
    - Dieter Groschel, Infectious Diseases/Microbiology, undated (Box-folder 2:36)
    - Frederick Hayden, Infectious Diseases, undated (Box-folder 2:37)
    - Nuzhet O. Atuk, Nephrology, circa 1956 (Box-folder 2:38)
      Photographed by Holsinger Studio
    - Frederic B. Westervelt, Jr., Nephrology, 1962 February 6 (Box-folder 2:39)
    - Nuzhet O. Atuk, Nephrology, 1965 December 29 (Box-folder 2:40)
    - Nuzhet O. Atuk, Nephrology, 1973 June 11 (Box-folder 2:41)
    - Andrew E. Lazar, Nephrology Resident, circa 2001 (Box-folder 2:42)
    - Nuzhet O. Atuk, Nephrology, undated (Box-folder 2:43)
    - Rasheed A. Balogun, Nephrology, undated (Box-folder 2:44)
    - Renal Unit, Nephrology, undated (Box-folder 2:45)
    - Paul Suratt, Pulmonary and Critical Care Division, 1989 November 16 (Box-folder 2:46)
    - Dudley F. Rochester, Pulmonary Medicine, 1991 (Box-folder 2:47)
    - Richard I. Enelow, Pulmonary and Critical Care Division, undated (Box-folder 2:48)
    - John L. Guerrant, Pulmonary Allergy Division, undated (Box-folder 2:49)
    - Rheumatology Group, with John Davis, 1987 (Box-folder 2:50)
    - Rheumatology Group, with Cathy? Murphy, 1988 (Box-folder 2:51)
    - John Davis, Rheumatology, 1989 November 21 (Box-folder 2:52)
    - Rheumatology Group, with John Davis, 1990 May 24 (Box-folder 2:53)
    - Rheumatology Group, with Cathy Murphy?, 1991 June (Box-folder 2:54)
    - Rheumatology Group, with Cathy Murphy?, 1992 (Box-folder 2:55)
    - Rheumatology Group, undated (Box-folder 2:56)
    - James Camp, Internal Medicine, 1960 (Box-folder 2:57)
    - Dr. Thomas Hunter (Internal Medicine) and Mrs. Hunter, 1960 September 6 (Box-folder 2:58)
    - Thomas H. Hunter, Internal Medicine, 1962 May 8 (Box-folder 2:59)
    - Thomas H. Hunter, Internal Medicine, 1966 July 29 (Box-folder 2:60)
    - Edward W. Hook, Internal Medicine, Chair (1969-1990), circa 1973 (Box-folder 2:61A)
    - Distinguished Achievement Award, presented to Edward W. Hook by the Center Alumni Council of New York Hospital—Cornell Medical Center, 1982 May 21 (Box-folder 2:61B)